<Asset>
  <Template>Text</Template>
  <Values>
    <Standard>
      <GUID>3942</GUID>
      <Name>ExpeditionInfoCornerInfotipText</Name>
    </Standard>
    <Text>
      <LocaText>
        <English>
          <Text>You can send ships on expeditions to discover animals and artifacts for your zoo and museum, rescue specialists to have them work in your city or capture pirates treasures. &lt;br /&gt;The fate of the expedition will be down to you. To succeed in an expedition, you should prepare correctly: &lt;br /&gt;- Rations are crucial aboard of your ship. They give moral to your crew and allow you to feed them between each obstacle their encounter. A starving crew loses more moral between each obstacle than a crew you feed. Moreover, you crew appreciates having different types of food. Feeding them with diverse rations will allow them to keep a higher moral than if you fed them with the same type of good over and over.&lt;br /&gt;- The threats indicates which kind of obstacles you are most likely to encounter. Each type of obstacle can be dealt with a specific attribute (ex: Naval Power is very helpful in the case of a Naval Battle threat). When preparing for a specific threat your captain warned you against, you are increasing the moral of your crew greatly.&lt;br /&gt;- To prepare for a threat, you must store in your ship a good or an item which possesses the related attribute. Ex: If the captain warns you about a wildlife threat, you should prepare to hunt. Hunting attribute can be found in goods such as fur coats or in specialist such as the Forester. In order to get the full number of the attribute indicated in the good, you need to store in the ship 50 units of that good.&lt;br /&gt;- Once facing an obstacle, you will have to take decision. Most of the times, decisions are linked to attributes. The better you are in the related attribute, the most chance you have to get the best outcome of this decision.&lt;br /&gt;- Expeditions have 3 different difficulties levels: Easy, Average and Hard, represented by skulls. An easy expedition will have less obstacles before you reach the reward, however the reward will be less rare than harder expedition. Moreover, it is easier to fill the moral bar of easy expedition. The hardest the expedition, the better items and goods you must store onboard in order to fill the moral bar. Hard expeditions are risky but finishing them is a certain way of getting legendary items.</Text>
          <ExportCount>1</ExportCount>
        </English>
      </LocaText>
      <LineID>14109</LineID>
    </Text>
  </Values>
</Asset>